<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Of Brews and Views</title><link>http://amitsethi.in</link><description>Amit Sethi's Blog</description><atom:link href="http://amitsethi.in/rss.xml" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self"></atom:link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2015 11:51:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>http://getnikola.com/</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Hello Interwebbers</title><link>http://amitsethi.in/posts/hello-world.html</link><dc:creator>Amit Sethi</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello, Kind visitor to this page. Welcome, I complement you that among the zillion pages you could have been visiting right now or of the thousands of cute cat pictures you could have been looking at, you chose to spend your time here and let me indulge in my narcissism. Its been about 2409 days since I had last written something that in common English could be described as a blog post. Although there was a time when "blogging" was the cornerstone of my creative expression. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am hoping that I could make this a regular event again. I am sorting out kinks in my "deployment pipeline" to make sure I can publish a blog in the quickest possible way preferrably from my editor itself. In this I have to thank this wonderful tool called &lt;a href="http://getnikola.com/"&gt;nikola&lt;/a&gt; and this beautiful &lt;a href="https://github.com/punchagan/lanyon"&gt;theme&lt;/a&gt; for nikola written by my friend Puneeth which has made me want to write a blog again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have come uptil here without getting distracted or bored I might as well tell you that I think I might know something more than the next person you meet on public transport on the subjects of writing code, programming languages (especially, &lt;a href="https://www.python.org/"&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt;), web development, &lt;a href="http://www.gnu.org/software/emacs/"&gt;Emacs&lt;/a&gt;, Literature, Philosophy and Economics. If any of those subjects kindle the intellectual fire in you, You might want to put this in your "feed".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>http://amitsethi.in/posts/hello-world.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2015 06:00:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>